idlehearts.com 2009-02-02

# Idlehearts! - Terms

### Subject: About IdleHearts and the Information We Collect.

**IdleHearts does not send Spam or sell email addresses.**

### Information submitted by Members to IdleHearts

IdleHearts is an online social networking community that connects people through networks of friends for communicating, sharing and making new friends and lovers. To accomplish this, each IdleHearts Member creates his or her own profile, which contains the personal information that the Member chooses to include. This personal information includes such things as:

  * Name of the Member (depending on the options selected by the Member),
  * Gender, age, martial status and other, similar personal information,
  * Occupation,
  * Schools attended or companies with whom the Member is associated,
  * Location (e.g., city and state), and
  * Photos or other shared content uploaded by the Member to his or her profile, to the extent that it includes personal information.

IdleHearts also collects Member-submitted account information such as name and email address to identify Members, send notifications related to the use of the IdleHearts service and conduct market research and marketing for IdleHearts's internal use only. You should also be aware that Members may reveal other personal information while communicating on other areas of the IdleHearts website, e.g., while participating in discussions on **IdleHearts Groups** and/or posting information on **IdleHearts Blogs**. This information, in turn, might be viewed by other Members or visitors to the IdleHearts website who are not Members.

### Subject:Use of Information Obtained by IdleHearts

### Display of Members' Information

Except where a Member might choose to include a full name in his or her profile, a Member's email address and full name will only be used in the following circumstances:

  * When the Member invites a friend via email to become a IdleHearts Member,
  * When the Member sends a request to another Member to add the other Member to his or her friend list,
  * When we send notifications to the Member relating to his or her use of the IdleHearts service or IdleHearts website, and
  * If the Member so chooses, when we send regular notifications, weekly updates, or other news regarding the IdleHearts service or the IdleHearts website.

Except when inviting or adding friends or as otherwise expressly set forth herein, a Member's email address will never be shared with or displayed to any other person. Members and their friends, and other Members within their personal networks (depending on the level of sharing a Member has chosen) communicate on IdleHearts with each other through the IdleHearts service, without disclosing email addresses.

### Use of Members' Information

### 

We use information relating to each Member's server information, IP address, and browser-type to display targeted third party advertisements.

### Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

Except as explained herein, or where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your Membership. However, IdleHearts may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to Members and other users of the IdleHearts website more targeted advertising, products and services; provided that, in such situations, we will never disclose information that would personally identify you. As set forth above, IdleHearts may (i) use your email address to conduct market research for IdleHearts's internal use only; and/or (ii) use your email address to market IdleHearts to you (e.g., new features and applications, announcements, opportunities of interest). IdleHearts may contract with a third party to conduct such research and marketing; provided that such third party will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality to IdleHearts and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by IdleHearts other than as expressly instructed by IdleHearts and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

### Links

The IdleHearts Website contains links to other websites. This includes links that are placed there by IdleHearts (such as in advertisements), as well as by other IdleHearts Members. Please be aware that IdleHearts is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage all Members and other users of the IdleHearts website to be aware of when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by IdleHearts through the IdleHearts website.

### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on the IdleHearts website. However, we do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any Member or other user of the IdleHearts website which they did not intentionally submit to us other than as stated in this Privacy Policy. We use both "session ID cookies" and "persistent cookies." We use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Note also that Members may optionally use a cookie to remember their email in order to automatically log in to our website. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browsers's "help" file; however, please note that, if you reject cookies or disable cookies in your web browser, you may not be able to use the IdleHearts website.

### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

REMEMBER THAT YOU CAN CHANGE THE GROUP OF PEOPLE WHO MAY VIEW YOUR PROFILE AT ANY TIME. YOU CAN CHANGE THESE PROFILE SHARING SETTINGS BY CLICKING THE "SETTINGS" LINK IN THE TOP, RIGHT CORNER OF THE IDLEHEARTS HOMEPAGE. ALSO, YOU CAN ALWAYS CHANGE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU'VE SUBMITTED TO THE IDLEHEARTS WEBSITE, INCLUDING THE INFORMATION INCLUDED IN YOUR PROFILE, BY CLICKING THE "EDIT PROFILE" LINK ON YOUR IDLEHEARTS PROFILE PAGE.

### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so Members and other users of the IdleHearts website are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use Members' or other users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify those Members and users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our website.

### Invite a Friend

If a Member elects to use our "Invite" feature to invite a friend to become a Member of the IdleHearts service, we ask them for that friend's email address. IdleHearts will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. IdleHearts stores this email address for the purpose of: (i) automatically adding the respondent to the “friends list” of the Member sending the invitation; (ii) sending reminders of the invitation and (iii) sending emails on recent updates by the Member on IdleHearts to the Member's invited friend. IdleHearts will never sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. Any person who receives an invitation may [contact IdleHearts](http://www.idlehearts.com/contact.php) to request the removal of this information from our database.

### Security

The IdleHearts account of every Member is password-protected. IdleHearts takes every precaution to protect the information of the Members, as well as information collected from other users of the IdleHearts website. We use industry standard measures to protect all information that is stored on our servers and within our database. We limit the access to this information to those employees who need access to perform their job function such as our customer service personnel. If you have any questions about the security at our website, please [contact us](http://www.idlehearts.com/contact.php).

### Email Choice/Opt-out

Members who no longer wish to receive our weekly email updates or other email notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by following the instructions contained in the applicable email or by logging-in and changing their settings in the "Account Settings" section of the IdleHearts website. You can access this page by clicking on the "Settings" link on the top right of your IdleHearts homepage.

### Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to Members by our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may use cookies. Doing this allows the ad network to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad networks may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. IdleHearts does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed on the computer of any Member or other user of the IdleHearts website by the third-party ad servers or ad networks. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by IdleHearts only, and does not cover the use of cookies by any other party.

### Contacting IdleHearts

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, IdleHearts's privacy practices, or your dealings with IdleHearts, please [contact us](http://www.idlehearts.com/contact.php).
